Office of the Vice-President, Finance and Administration fonds
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department
- Administrative departments, 1966 - 1984; F-28-3; 1.54 m of textual records
  - Personnel - Faculty of Arts, 1972 - 1979; F-28-3-0-0-85 (Archival box - standard 28-17)
  - Personnel - Faculty of Arts, 1973; F-28-3-0-0-86 (Archival box - standard 28-17)
  - Personnel - Faculty of Arts, 1968 - 1971; F-28-3-0-0-87 (Archival box - standard 28-17)
  - Personnel - Faculty of Arts, 1971; F-28-3-0-0-88 (Archival box - standard 28-17)
  - Personnel - Faculty of Arts, 1970; F-28-3-0-0-89 (Archival box - standard 28-17)
  - Personnel - Faculty of Education, 1971; F-28-3-0-0-90 (Archival box - standard 28-17)
  - Personnel - Faculty of Science, 1974 - 1976; F-28-3-0-0-91 (Archival box - standard 28-17)
  - Personnel - Library, 1972 - 1976; F-28-3-0-0-92 (Archival box - standard 28-17)
  - Personnel - Safety Officer, 1977; F-28-3-0-0-93 (Archival box - standard 28-17)
    File consists of correspondence received or copied to the Vice-President, Academic relating to the activities of the Fire and Saftey Officer. Includes a report on SFU emergency lighting and power, and correspondence with the BC Occupational Environment Branch relating to the premises of the SFU Library building.
  - Personnel - Physical Plant and Planning, 1968 - 1975; F-28-3-0-0-94 (Archival box - standard 28-17)
  - Physical Plant and Planning, 1970 - 1973; F-28-3-0-0-95 (Archival box - standard 28-17)
  - Physical Plant and Planning, 1974 - 1975; F-28-3-0-0-96 (Archival box - standard 28-17)
  - Physical Plant and Planning, 1976 - 1977; F-28-3-0-0-97 (Archival box - standard 28-18)
  - Physical Plant and Planning, 1978 - 1979; F-28-3-0-0-98 (Archival box - standard 28-18)
  - P.P.P.- Building and Residences - Admin Building, 1972 - 1975; F-28-3-0-0-99 (Archival box - standard 28-18)
  - P.P.P.- Building and Residences - Day Care Centre, 1972 - 1976; F-28-3-0-0-100 (Archival box - standard 28-18)
  - P.P.P.- Building and Residences - French Lang Train Centre, 1974; F-28-3-0-0-101 (Archival box - standard 28-18)
  - P.P.P.- Building and Residences - Gymnasium, 1972 - 1978; F-28-3-0-0-102 (Archival box - standard 28-18)
  - P.P.P.- Building and Residences - Ice Rink, 1973 - 1974; F-28-3-0-0-103 (Archival box - standard 28-18)
  - P.P.P.- Building and Residences - Images Theatre, 1978; F-28-3-0-0-104 (Archival box - standard 28-18)
  - P.P.P.- Building and Residences - Library, 1972 - 1981; F-28-3-0-0-105 (Archival box - standard 28-18)
  - P.P.P.- Building and Residences - Multi-Purpose Complex, 1978 - 1981; F-28-3-0-0-106 (Archival box - standard 28-18)
  - P.P.P.- Building and Residences - Residences, 1971; F-28-3-0-0-107 (Archival box - standard 28-18)
  - P.P.P.- Building and Residences - South Court Lounge, 1976 - 1981; F-28-3-0-0-108 (Archival box - standard 28-18)
  - P.P.P.- Building and Residences - Teaching and Office Space, 1971 - 1979; F-28-3-0-0-109 (Archival box - standard 28-19)
  - P.P.P.- Building and Residences - Teaching and Lab Complex, 1978; F-28-3-0-0-110 (Archival box - standard 28-19)
  - P.P.P.- Building and Residences - University Centre, 1970 - 1972; F-28-3-0-0-111 (Archival box - standard 28-19)
  - P.P.P.- Building and Residences - University Village, 1974 - 1978; F-28-3-0-0-112 (Archival box - standard 28-19)
  - P.P.P.- Building and Residences - University Centre, 1981; F-28-3-0-0-113 (Archival box - standard 28-19)
  - P.P.P.- Building and Residences - West Mall Complex, 1981; F-28-3-0-0-114 (Archival box - standard 28-19)
  - P.P.P.- Grounds and Landscaping, 1971 - 1981; F-28-3-0-0-115 (Archival box - standard 28-19)
  - P.P.P.- Buildings and Residences - Outdoor Education Training Centre, 1972; F-28-3-0-0-116 (Archival box - standard 28-19)
  - Residences, 1981 - 1984; F-28-3-0-0-117 (Archival box - standard 28-19)
  - Athletics and Recreation - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1978; F-28-3-0-0-118 (Archival box - standard 28-43)
  - Ancillary Services - Winter Sports Complex Feasibility Study, 1973; F-28-3-0-0-119 (Archival box - standard 28-43)
  - P.P.P. - Playfield Facilities Study, 1972; F-28-3-0-0-120 (Archival box - standard 28-43)
- Memoranda, 1969 - 1981; F-28-4; 23 cm of textual records
  Series consists of memoranda the Vice-President sent to or received from other bodies within the University. These other bodies include faculties, departments and other Vice-Presidents. The series includes memoranda and reports.
  - Analytical Studies, 1976 - 1977; F-28-4-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 28-20)
  - Faculty of Arts, 1970 - 1979; F-28-4-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 28-20)
  - Faculty of Continuing Studies, 1971 - 1977; F-28-4-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 28-20)
  - Faculty of Education, 1969 - 1981; F-28-4-0-0-4 (Archival box - standard 28-20)
  - Faculty of Interdisciplinary Studies, 1977 - 1979; F-28-4-0-0-5 (Archival box - standard 28-20)
  - Faculty of Graduate Studies, 1971 - 1981; F-28-4-0-0-6 (Archival box - standard 28-20)
  - Faculty of Science, 1970 - 1974; F-28-4-0-0-7 (Archival box - standard 28-20)
  - Vice-President, Academic, 1970 - 1981; F-28-4-0-0-8 (Archival box - standard 28-20)
  - Vice-President, Development, 1970 - 1981; F-28-4-0-0-9 (Archival box - standard 28-20)
  - Vice-President, University Services, 1971 - 1976; F-28-4-0-0-10 (Archival box - standard 28-20)
  - Vice-President, University Services - Residences, 1972 - 1977; F-28-4-0-0-11 (Archival box - standard 28-20)
  - Vice-President, University Services - Arts Centre, 1972 - 1976; F-28-4-0-0-12 (Archival box - standard 28-21)
  - Vice-President, University Services - Resources Office, 1974 - 1977; F-28-4-0-0-13 (Archival box - standard 28-21)
  - Vice-President, University Services - Health Services, 1974 - 1978; F-28-4-0-0-14 (Archival box - standard 28-21)
  - Student Society, 1971 - 1974; F-28-4-0-0-15 (Archival box - standard 28-21)
  - Student Society, 1974 - 1981; F-28-4-0-0-16 (Archival box - standard 28-21)
  - Student Services, 1977 - 1978; F-28-4-0-0-17 (Archival box - standard 28-21)
  - Student Services, 1979; F-28-4-0-0-18 (Archival box - standard 28-21)
  - Student Services, 1981; F-28-4-0-0-19 (Archival box - standard 28-21)
- External relations, 1973 - 1981; F-28-5; 16 cm of textual records
  Series consists of records relating to the liaison of the Vice-President with various external bodies, including the Universities Council, other universities, associations, and municipalities. It includes correspondence, memoranda, and reports.
  - Associations, 1974 - 1976; F-28-5-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 28-22)
  - Associations, 1977 - 1979; F-28-5-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 28-22)
  - Universities Council, 1975; F-28-5-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 28-22)
  - Universities Council, 1976; F-28-5-0-0-4 (Archival box - standard 28-22)
  - Universities Council, 1978; F-28-5-0-0-5 (Archival box - standard 28-22)
  - Universities - Notre Dame, 1974; F-28-5-0-0-6 (Archival box - standard 28-22)
  - Universities - U.B.C., 1978 - 1981; F-28-5-0-0-7 (Archival box - standard 28-22)
  - Universities - U. Vic., 1978; F-28-5-0-0-8 (Archival box - standard 28-22)
  - Municipalities - Burnaby, 1973 - 1979; F-28-5-0-0-9 (Archival box - standard 28-22)
  - Municipalities - Coquitlam, 1975 - 1979; F-28-5-0-0-10 (Archival box - standard 28-23)
  - Municipalities - Port Moody, 1979; F-28-5-0-0-11 (Archival box - standard 28-23)
  - Government, 1981; F-28-5-0-0-12 (Archival box - standard 28-23)
  - Consultant - Iona Campagnolo, 1980; F-28-5-0-0-13 (Archival box - standard 28-23)
- Personal material, 1970 - 1980; F-28-6; 17 cm of textual records
  Series consists of records relating to the personal correspondence, private and professional activities, as well as those in which the Vice-President represented the university. It includes correspondence, memoranda, reports, post-cards and day-timers.
  - Correspondence, 1972 - 1979; F-28-6-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 28-42)
    Restricted in part
  - Speeches, 1975 - 1977; F-28-6-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 28-42)
  - Daybooks, 1980; F-28-6-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 28-42)
  - Personal Correspondence, 1970; F-28-6-0-0-4 (Archival box - standard 28-42)
  - Personal Correspondence, 1971; F-28-6-0-0-5 (Archival box - standard 28-42)
  - Personal Correspondence, 1972; F-28-6-0-0-6 (Archival box - standard 28-43)
  - Personal Correspondence, 1973; F-28-6-0-0-7 (Archival box - standard 28-43)
  - Personal Correspondence, 1974; F-28-6-0-0-8 (Archival box - standard 28-43)
- Committees, 1966 - 1984; F-28-7; 2.34 m of textual records
  Series consists of records of relating to the Vice-President's involvement or correspondence with various university committees, including committees established by and reporting to the Vice-President.
  The series was separated from the body of the fonds during the original archival arrangement and description. Its description has been reintegrated into the fonds without a physical re-arrangement.
  - Ad hoc committees, 1969 - 1982; F-28-7-1; 13 cm of textual records
    - Ad Hoc Committee on Patents, 1969; F-28-7-1-0-1 (Archival box - standard 28-25)
    - Ad Hoc Committee on Implementation of the Ellis Report, 1969; F-28-7-1-0-2 (Archival box - standard 28-25)
    - Ad Hoc Committee on Microfilm, 1975; F-28-7-1-0-3 (Archival box - standard 28-25)
    - Task Force on Financial Support to the Day Care Centre, 1982; F-28-7-1-0-4 (Archival box - standard 28-25)
    - Ad Hoc Committee - Special Bonus Agenda, Minutes, Correspondence, Report, 1974; F-28-7-1-0-5 (Archival box - standard 28-25)
    - Ad Hoc Committee - Special Bonus Eligibility and Submissions, 1974; F-28-7-1-0-6 (Archival box - standard 28-25)
    - Ad Hoc Committee - Extended Services, 1977; F-28-7-1-0-7 (Archival box - standard 28-25)
    - Ad Hoc Committee: Resource Allocation; Terms of Reference and Papers, 1975 - 1976; F-28-7-1-0-8 (Archival box - standard 28-25)
    - Professional Development Committee, 1977 - 1978; F-28-7-1-0-9 (Archival box - standard 28-25)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-22-8-6-0-13.
  - Open House and Anniversary Committees, 1972 - 1984; F-28-7-2; 38 cm of textual records
    - Open House - Miscellaneous, 1972; F-28-7-2-0-1 (Archival box - standard 28-26)
    - Complete report of first Open House, 1972; F-28-7-2-0-2 (Archival box - standard 28-26)
    - Vice-Pres. file - Open House, 1972; F-28-7-2-0-3 (Archival box - standard 28-26)
    - Vice-Pres. file - Open House, 1972; F-28-7-2-0-4 (Archival box - standard 28-26)
    - 10th Anniversary Celebrations VPUS Files (KC Aug. 1991), 1975; F-28-7-2-0-5 (Archival box - standard 28-26)
    - University Services - Open House - Recommendations of the Steering committee for the next Open House, 1972; F-28-7-2-0-6 (Archival box - standard 28-26)
    - Open House, F-28-7-2-0-7 (Archival box - standard 28-26)
    - University Services - Tenth Anniversary Celebrations - Open House, 1975; F-28-7-2-0-8 (Archival box - standard 28-26)
    - Open House, 1975; F-28-7-2-0-9
    - Miscellaneous handouts, clippings and publications re Open House, 1980; F-28-7-2-0-10 (Archival box - standard 28-26)
    - SFU Open House buttons, F-28-7-2-0-11 (Archival box - standard 28-26)
    - Open House - Projects committee, 1975; F-28-7-2-0-12 (Archival box - standard 28-27)
    - Open House - Projects committee - Schedules, 1975; F-28-7-2-0-13 (Archival box - standard 28-27)
    - Open House - General projects and functions, #1, 1978; F-28-7-2-0-14 (Archival box - standard 28-27)
    - Open House - General projects and functions, #2, 1978; F-28-7-2-0-15 (Archival box - standard 28-27)
    - Open House - Forms, budget, etc., 1978; F-28-7-2-0-16 (Archival box - standard 28-27)
    - Open House - miscellaneous pamphlets, F-28-7-2-0-17 (Archival box - standard 28-27)
    - Open House, 1978; F-28-7-2-0-18 (Archival box - standard 28-27)
    - Open House - General projects and functions, 1980; F-28-7-2-0-19 (Archival box - standard 28-27)
    - Open House - General projects and functions, #1, 1983; F-28-7-2-0-20 (Archival box - standard 28-27)
    - Open House - General projects and functions, #2, 1983; F-28-7-2-0-21 (Archival box - standard 28-27)
    - Correspondence, 1984; F-28-7-2-0-22 (Archival box - standard 28-27)
  - Information System Committee, 1970 - 1981; F-28-7-3; 12 cm of textual records
    - Terms of Reference, 1970 - 1972; F-28-7-3-0-1 (Archival box - standard 28-28)
    - Agenda and Minutes, 1970 - 1976; F-28-7-3-0-2 (Archival box - standard 28-28)
    - Report, 1974; F-28-7-3-0-3 (Archival box - standard 28-28)
    - Correspondence, 1970 - 1974; F-28-7-3-0-4 (Archival box - standard 28-28)
    - Papers, 1975 - 1976; F-28-7-3-0-5 (Archival box - standard 28-28)
    - Papers, 1976; F-28-7-3-0-6 (Archival box - standard 28-28)
    - Memoranda, 1976 - 1978; F-28-7-3-0-7 (Archival box - standard 28-28)
    - Papers, 1977; F-28-7-3-0-8 (Archival box - standard 28-28)
    - Papers, 1977 - 1981; F-28-7-3-0-9 (Archival box - standard 28-28)
    - Data Base System, 1976; F-28-7-3-0-10 (Archival box - standard 28-28)
    - Data Base System, 1977; F-28-7-3-0-11 (Archival box - standard 28-28)
    - Report of External Review Committee on the Computing Centre at SFU, 1975; F-28-7-3-0-12 (Archival box - standard 28-28)
  - Intercollegiate Athletics Review Committee, 1971; F-28-7-4; 3 cm of textual records
    - Papers, 1971; F-28-7-4-0-1 (Archival box - standard 28-43)
    - Report, 1971; F-28-7-4-0-2 (Archival box - standard 28-43)
  - Athletics and Recreation Advisory Committee, 1976 - 1984; F-28-7-5; 5 cm of textual records
    - Minutes of Meetings, 1977 - 1980; F-28-7-5-0-1 (Archival box - standard 28-23)
    - Minutes of Meetings, 1982 - 1984; F-28-7-5-0-2 (Archival box - standard 28-23)
    - Papers, 1982 - 1984; F-28-7-5-0-3 (Archival box - standard 28-23)
    - Report, 1983; F-28-7-5-0-4 (Archival box - standard 28-23)
    - Supplementary Funding Proposal, 1984; F-28-7-5-0-5 (Archival box - standard 28-23)
    - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1976 - 1980; F-28-7-5-0-6 (Archival box - standard 28-23)
  - Faculty Search Committees, 1966 - 1976; F-28-7-6; 12 cm of textual records
    - Dean of Arts, 1966; F-28-7-6-0-1 (Archival box - standard 28-29)
    - Dean of Arts, 1970; F-28-7-6-0-2 (Archival box - standard 28-29)
    - Dean of Arts, 1970; F-28-7-6-0-3 (Archival box - standard 28-29)
    - Dean of Science, 1970; F-28-7-6-0-4 (Archival box - standard 28-29)
    - Dean of Arts, 1971; F-28-7-6-0-5 (Archival box - standard 28-29)
    - Dean of Graduate Studies, 1971; F-28-7-6-0-6 (Archival box - standard 28-29)
    - Dean of Education, 1971 - 1972; F-28-7-6-0-7 (Archival box - standard 28-29)
    - Dean of Graduate Studies, 1972; F-28-7-6-0-8 (Archival box - standard 28-29)
    - Dean of Arts, 1973; F-28-7-6-0-9 (Archival box - standard 28-29)
    - Dean of Arts, 1973; F-28-7-6-0-10 (Archival box - standard 28-29)
    - Dean of Interdisciplinary Studiess, 1973; F-28-7-6-0-11 (Archival box - standard 28-29)
    - Dean of Continuing Studies, 1973; F-28-7-6-0-12 (Archival box - standard 28-29)
    - Dean of Science, 1975; F-28-7-6-0-13 (Archival box - standard 28-29)
    - Dean of Arts, 1976; F-28-7-6-0-14 (Archival box - standard 28-29)
    - Dean of Education, 1976; F-28-7-6-0-15 (Archival box - standard 28-29)
  - Deans' Meetings, 1970 - 1984; F-28-7-7; 62 cm of textual records
    - Agenda and Minutes; Agenda, Minutes, Papers, 1970 - 1971; F-28-7-7-0-1 (Archival box - standard 28-30)
    - Agenda, Minutes, Papers, 1972; F-28-7-7-0-2 (Archival box - standard 28-30)
    - Agenda, Minutes, Papers, 1973; F-28-7-7-0-3 (Archival box - standard 28-30)
    - Agenda, 1974; F-28-7-7-0-4 (Archival box - standard 28-30)
    - Papers, 1974; F-28-7-7-0-5 (Archival box - standard 28-30)
    - Papers, 1974; F-28-7-7-0-6 (Archival box - standard 28-30)
    - Papers, 1974; F-28-7-7-0-7 (Archival box - standard 28-30)
    - Papers, 1974; F-28-7-7-0-8 (Archival box - standard 28-30)
    - Agenda, 1975; F-28-7-7-0-9 (Archival box - standard 28-31)
    - Papers, 1975; F-28-7-7-0-10 (Archival box - standard 28-31)
    - Papers, 1975; F-28-7-7-0-11 (Archival box - standard 28-31)
    - Papers, 1974; F-28-7-7-0-12 (Archival box - standard 28-31)
    - Agenda, 1976; F-28-7-7-0-13 (Archival box - standard 28-31)
    - Papers, 1976; F-28-7-7-0-14 (Archival box - standard 28-31)
    - Papers, 1976; F-28-7-7-0-15 (Archival box - standard 28-31)
    - Papers, 1976; F-28-7-7-0-16 (Archival box - standard 28-31)
    - Agenda and Minutes, 1977; F-28-7-7-0-17 (Archival box - standard 28-31)
    - Papers, D-77-1 to D-77-14, 1977; F-28-7-7-0-18 (Archival box - standard 28-31)
    - Papers, D-77-15 to D-77-34, 1977; F-28-7-7-0-19 (Archival box - standard 28-31)
    - Correspondence, 1977; F-28-7-7-0-20 (Archival box - standard 28-31)
    - Agenda and Minutes, 1978; F-28-7-7-0-21 (Archival box - standard 28-32)
    - Papers, D-78-1 to D-78-16, 1978; F-28-7-7-0-22 (Archival box - standard 28-32)
    - Papers, D-78-17 to D-78-39, 1978; F-28-7-7-0-23 (Archival box - standard 28-32)
    - Papers, D-78-40 to D-78-57, 1978; F-28-7-7-0-24 (Archival box - standard 28-32)
    - Papers, D-78-58 to D-78-68, 1978; F-28-7-7-0-25 (Archival box - standard 28-32)
    - Papers, D-78-69 to D-78-87, 1978; F-28-7-7-0-26 (Archival box - standard 28-32)
    - Memoranda, 1978; F-28-7-7-0-27 (Archival box - standard 28-32)
    - Memoranda, 1978; F-28-7-7-0-28 (Archival box - standard 28-32)
    - Agenda and Minutes, 1979; F-28-7-7-0-29 (Archival box - standard 28-32)
    - Papers, D-79-01 to D-79-15, 1979; F-28-7-7-0-30 (Archival box - standard 28-32)
    - Papers, D-79-16 to D-79-29, 1979; F-28-7-7-0-31 (Archival box - standard 28-32)
    - Papers, D-79-30 to D-79-71, 1979; F-28-7-7-0-32 (Archival box - standard 28-32)
    - Memoranda, 1979; F-28-7-7-0-33 (Archival box - standard 28-33)
    - Memoranda, 1979; F-28-7-7-0-34 (Archival box - standard 28-33)
    - Agenda and Minutes, 1980; F-28-7-7-0-35 (Archival box - standard 28-33)
    - Papers, D-80-01 to D-80-22, 1980; F-28-7-7-0-36 (Archival box - standard 28-33)
    - Papers, D-80-23 to D-80-33, 1980; F-28-7-7-0-37 (Archival box - standard 28-33)
    - Papers, D-80-34 to D-80-56, 1980; F-28-7-7-0-38 (Archival box - standard 28-33)
    - Papers, D-80-57 to D-80-78, 1980; F-28-7-7-0-39 (Archival box - standard 28-33)
    - Memoranda, 1980; F-28-7-7-0-40 (Archival box - standard 28-33)
    - Memoranda, 1980; F-28-7-7-0-41 (Archival box - standard 28-33)
    - Agenda and Minutes, 1980; F-28-7-7-0-42 (Archival box - standard 28-33)
    - Agenda and Minutes, 1981; F-28-7-7-0-43 (Archival box - standard 28-33)
    - Agenda and Minutes, 1981; F-28-7-7-0-44 (Archival box - standard 28-33)
    - Papers, D-81-01 to D-81-30, 1981; F-28-7-7-0-45 (Archival box - standard 28-33)
    - Agenda and Minutes, 1982; F-28-7-7-0-46 (Archival box - standard 28-34)
    - Agenda and Minutes, 1982; F-28-7-7-0-47 (Archival box - standard 28-34)
    - Papers, D-82-01 to D-82-27, 1982; F-28-7-7-0-48 (Archival box - standard 28-34)
    - Papers, D-82-28 to D-82-56, 1982; F-28-7-7-0-49 (Archival box - standard 28-34)
    - Memoranda, 1983; F-28-7-7-0-50 (Archival box - standard 28-34)
    - Agenda and Minutes, 1983; F-28-7-7-0-51 (Archival box - standard 28-34)
    - Agenda and Minutes, 1983; F-28-7-7-0-52 (Archival box - standard 28-34)
    - Papers, D-83-02 to D-83-18, 1983; F-28-7-7-0-53 (Archival box - standard 28-34)
    - Papers, D-83-19 to D-83-47, 1983; F-28-7-7-0-54 (Archival box - standard 28-34)
    - Agenda and Minutes, 1984; F-28-7-7-0-55 (Archival box - standard 28-34)
    - Agenda and Minutes, 1984; F-28-7-7-0-56 (Archival box - standard 28-34)
  - Vice-Presidential Review Committee, 1973 - 1975; F-28-7-8; 19 cm of textual records
    - Terms of Reference and Memoranda, 1974; F-28-7-8-0-1 (Archival box - small 28-35)
    - Miscellaneous memos and reports, 1974 - 1975; F-28-7-8-0-2 (Archival box - small 28-35)
    - Memoranda, 1975; F-28-7-8-0-3 (Archival box - small 28-35)
    - Memoranda, 1975; F-28-7-8-0-4 (Archival box - small 28-35)
    - Memoranda, 1975; F-28-7-8-0-5 (Archival box - small 28-35)
    - Memoranda, 1975; F-28-7-8-0-6 (Archival box - small 28-35)
    - Memoranda, 1974; F-28-7-8-0-7 (Archival box - small 28-35)
    - Miscecllaneous Memos and Reports, 1973 - 1974; F-28-7-8-0-8 (Archival box - standard 28-36)
  - Management Review Committee, 1977 - 1978; F-28-7-9; 6 cm of textual records
    - Binder: Agenda, Minutes, Papers, Memoranda of Committtee, vol. 1, 1977 - 1978; F-28-7-9-0-1 (Archival box - standard 28-36)
    - Binder: Agenda, Minutes, Papers, Memoranda of Committtee, vol. 2, 1977 - 1978; F-28-7-9-0-2 (Archival box - standard 28-36)
    - Binder: Agenda, Minutes, Papers, Memoranda of Committtee, vol. 3, 1977 - 1978; F-28-7-9-0-3 (Archival box - standard 28-36)
  - Advisory Committee on Ethnic Relations, 1980 - 1984; F-28-7-10; 3 cm of textual records
    - Terms of Reference, 1980; F-28-7-10-0-1 (Archival box - small 28-37)
    - Agenda and Minutes, 1980 - 1981; F-28-7-10-0-2 (Archival box - small 28-37)
    - Memoranda, 1984; F-28-7-10-0-3 (Archival box - small 28-37)
  - Committee to Reduce Paper Costs, 1976; F-28-7-11; 1 cm of textual records
    - Report and Papers, 1976; F-28-7-11-0-1 (Archival box - small 28-37)
  - Recruitment Committee, 1971 - 1972; F-28-7-12; 2 cm of textual records
    - Agenda, Minutes, and Papers, 1971 - 1972; F-28-7-12-0-1 (Archival box - small 28-37)
    - Subcommittee on Publications - Minutes, 1971 - 1972; F-28-7-12-0-2 (Archival box - small 28-37)
  - KNOW/SFU Projects Consultative Committee, 1981 - 1982; F-28-7-13; 6 cm of textual records
    - Terms of Reference, 1981; F-28-7-13-0-1 (Archival box - small 28-37)
    - Agenda and minutes, 1981; F-28-7-13-0-2 (Archival box - small 28-37)
    - Agenda and minutes, 1981; F-28-7-13-0-3 (Archival box - small 28-37)
    - Agenda and minutes, 1981; F-28-7-13-0-4 (Archival box - small 28-37)
    - Agenda and minutes, 1982; F-28-7-13-0-5 (Archival box - small 28-37)
  - Duplicating and Photocopying Committee, 1980; F-28-7-14; 6 cm of textual records
    - Terms of Reference, 1980; F-28-7-14-0-1 (Archival box - small 28-38)
    - Minutes of Meetings, 1980; F-28-7-14-0-2 (Archival box - small 28-38)
    - Reports, 1980; F-28-7-14-0-3 (Archival box - small 28-38)
    - Correspondence, 1980; F-28-7-14-0-4 (Archival box - small 28-38)
  - Administrative Policies and Procedures Committee, 1978 - 1980; F-28-7-15; 7 cm of textual records
    - Terms of Reference and Membership, 1978; F-28-7-15-0-1 (Archival box - small 28-38)
    - Minutes of Meetings, 1978; F-28-7-15-0-2 (Archival box - small 28-38)
    - Report, 1980; F-28-7-15-0-3 (Archival box - small 28-38)
    - Correspondence, 1978 - 1980; F-28-7-15-0-4 (Archival box - small 28-38)
    - Revised Policies and Procedures, 1980; F-28-7-15-0-5 (Archival box - small 28-38)
  - Interior Program Planning Committee, 1977 - 1979; F-28-7-16; 26 cm of textual records
    - Correspondence, 1977; F-28-7-16-0-1 (Archival box - standard 28-39)
    - Correspondence, 1977; F-28-7-16-0-2 (Archival box - standard 28-39)
    - Correspondence, 1977; F-28-7-16-0-3 (Archival box - standard 28-39)
    - Correspondence, 1977; F-28-7-16-0-4 (Archival box - standard 28-39)
    - Correspondence, 1977; F-28-7-16-0-5 (Archival box - standard 28-39)
    - Agenda and minutes, 1977; F-28-7-16-0-6 (Archival box - standard 28-39)
    - Papers, 1977; F-28-7-16-0-7 (Archival box - standard 28-39)
    - Papers, 1977; F-28-7-16-0-8 (Archival box - standard 28-39)
    - Draft Proposal for Interior, 1977; F-28-7-16-0-9 (Archival box - standard 28-39)
    - Reports for Discussion, 1977; F-28-7-16-0-10 (Archival box - standard 28-40)
    - Regional Meetings, 1977; F-28-7-16-0-11 (Archival box - standard 28-40)